[Music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]
I come to visit you, I come to visit you, my brothers,
tôi đện thăm tôi đến thăm các
on the old battlefield. You left and
anh nơi chiến tr trường xưa anh ra đi
never returned, you
không trở
forever lie on the land you love. Oh, my
mãi nằm lại nơi mạnh đất anh yêu
soldier, I come to visit you, my son, with
sĩ tôi đến thăm con
tearful eyes. I come to visit you, my brothers, the village, filled with the
ơi mắt lệ nho tôi đến thăm các anh thôn
love of that day.
thức tình non
You
ấy các anh ra
left, that day,
đi ngày
for your homeland, you hurried on
ấy vì quê hương các anh vội V vội V lên
the road to the battlefield, even
đường nơi chiến trường nêm mật nm ngay
though you
dù
welcomed the bustling
cho đón thu xôn
autumn, even
x dù
though bombs tore apart your hearts and
cho bom đàn xé nát xé nát tâm
bodies, your clothes were tattered and torn. In the
thân áo quần rách nát ngượng Màu Đào nơi
deep trenches or the mountains, you remained
chiến hào số sâu hay núi nghiệm các anh
steadfast, you stood tall, you held your
vẫn nhiên ngang vẫn hiên ngang ngẩng cao
heads high. You lay
đầu anh nằm
down, embracing the mountains, you sacrificed
xuống ôm tròn núi xong đây anh H sinh
for the beautiful country of
cho đất nước tươi đẹp ngày hôm
today. I come
nay tôi đến
here, my dear, with heartfelt gratitude. My dear
đây ngườii kh Tâm Tình Mãi Biết Ơn Người
soldier, I come
chiế sĩ năm nào tôi đ đến
here to send my heartfelt feelings to my country,
đâi gửi khúc tâm tình bất nước mình mãi
forever grateful.
mãi một niểm ơ
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Oh, my
ng
brothers, you
ơi các anh ra
left on that day,
đi ngày
for your homeland, you hurried on
ơi vì quê hương các anh vội V vội ph lên
the road to the battlefield.  Secret of the South,
đường nơi chiến trường nêm mật Nam
girls, even though they
gái Dù
welcome autumn, the
cho đón thu x
bombs, the shattered trees, the torn
chó bom đàn x nát xế náp tâm
clothes, dyed peach-colored, in the
thân áo quần rạch nan nhuộm màu đào nơi
deep trenches or the majestic mountains, the soldiers
chiến đào số sâu hay núi nghiêm các anh
still stand tall, still hold their
vẫn nhên ngang vẫn hiên ngang ngẩng cao
heads high, they
đầu anh còm
embrace the mountains, they go forth, they give birth
xống ôm trọn núi xong đy anh H sinh cho
to a beautiful country
đến nước tươi đẹp ngày hôm
today, I come
nay tôi đến
here to smile, a song of gratitude, forever grateful to the
đây cười Khúc Tâm Tình Mãi Biết Ơn Người
soldiers of yesteryear, I
chiế sĩ năm nào tôi đến
send this song of gratitude to the country,
nơi Gửi khúc tâm tình đất nước m
forever a memory of
mãi mãi một niệm
gratitude to
ơn đất nước
my country, forever
mình mãi
a
một
memory of
niệm
gratitude.
ơ a
[music]
[âm nhạc]